<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[Fuu] Nudist's Evasion</name>
  <author>Fuu Chan</author>
  <packageId>Fuu.NudistsEvasion</packageId>
  <description>
Backstory:
While there are obvious disadvantages to not having armor or protective clothing, it would be a mistake to underestimate the speed, agility, and footwork of an unhindered warrior. 

To increase the diversity of apparel choices and viability of nudist playthroughs, this mod gives lightly armored and naked colonists a bonus to their melee dodge and a new ranged evasion mechanic.

Primary Changes:
When someone has an equipped apparel mass of less than 6 kg (configurable in options), they will increasingly gain the following bonuses until reaching the maximum bonus when they're fully naked:
1. 40% Melee dodge.
2. 40% Ranged evasion.
3. 20% Movement speed when drafted.
(The ability to dodge and evade goes down as colonists' movement ability goes down!)
(Values also configurable in the options).

Instead of only wearing heavy armor, dodge/evasion builds using lighter armors are now possible! While potentially riskier, lightly armored and Nudist playthroughs are now very much a viable alternative!

(Bonuses apply multiplicatively to the existing accuracy formula, so there will never be a 100% chance to dodge or for a shot to miss).

*Optimized for performance.
*Safe to add mid-game.
*Safe to remove mid-game, but undraft everyone first.
*Humanoid Alien Races' races compatible.
*NOT Compatible with CE. They use their own combat system.
*No other known conflicts.

~2.1c update: Added "DisappearsOnDeath" to the Nudist's Swiftness buff, to prevent it from being listed as a cause of death when a pawn dies due to another reason.

~2.1b update: Changed setting "Only apply to player controlled colonists and slaves" to default to True. Otherwise this mod can make certain humanoid-based raids stronger than intended since the extra evade/dodge isn't taken into account by the raid points system.

~2.1 update: "Apparel Mass" no longer includes Utility items. Maximum movement speed buff when drafted increased to 20% from 15%. Apparel Mass in stats page shows decimal values now.

~2.0 update: Dodge and evasion have been reworked to scale based on "Apparel Mass", which enables all types of light armor evasion builds instead of being useful only for nudism playthroughs! In addition, balance has been adjusted after mathing and testing various values. Existing users are recommended to the go the mod options and press "Reset" to update to the latest values!

Github Link: https://github.com/tenguin/Rimworld_NudistsEvasion

Credits to: personal ami and Ninomae Ina'nis for the artwork used in the thumbnail and tanosii_chan for the upvote animation! Give them a visit!
  </description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>