<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[Fuu] Nudist's Evasion</name>
  <author>Fuu Chan</author>
  <packageId>Fuu.NudistsEvasion</packageId>
  <description>
To the naive space dweller, it would be easy to rule out Rimworld's nudist tribes as simple primatives. But in reality, they are more akin to body cults; Ideologies dedicated to perfecting the body.

Intense daily training, physical competitions, competitive sports, monster hunts, and gladiator fights. Starting from childhood they begin their training.

While there are obvious disadvantages to not having armor or protective clothing, it would be a huge mistake to underestimate the speed, agility, and fighting prowess of these lithe warriors.

When someone is "Fully nude" or wearing "Pants at most" and has the "Required Belief" (Meme/Precept/or None, configurable in options), they will gain:

1. 50% Melee Dodge (40% when wearing pants)
2. 50% Ranged Evasion (40% when wearing pants)
3. 20% Movement Speed when Drafted (15% when wearing pants)

(Values configurable in the options!)

Instead of tanking damage through armor, Nudist's rely on sheer evasion and speed. While risky, hopefully this makes a Nudist playthrough a viable alternative!

(Calculations follow the vanilla ranged accuracy formula, multiplicative, so there will never be a 100% chance to dodge or 100% chance to miss)

*Optimized for performance.
*Safe to add mid-game.
*Safe to remove mid-game, but undraft everyone first.
*Humanoid Alien Races' races compatible.
*Rocketman compatible.
*Rimthreaded compatible.
*NOT Compatible with CE. They use their own combat system.
*No other known conflicts.

Github Link: https://github.com/tenguin/Rimworld_NudistsEvasion

Credits to: personal ami and Ninomae Ina'nis for the artwork used in the thumbnail and tanosii_chan for the upvote animation! Give them a visit!
  </description>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.3</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</packageId>
      <displayName>Rimworld Ideology</displayName>
    </li>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Royalty</li>
    <li>Ludeon.RimWorld.Ideology</li>
    <li>brrainz.harmony</li>
  </loadAfter>
</ModMetaData>